(
"ai_sub_version": "1.11.0",
"subtitles_prompt_version": 3,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": "gemini-cli:gemini-3-flash-preview",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true
),
"gemini_cli": (
"timeout": 600
)
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": true,
"fps": 1,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"threshold_mb": 20,
"encoder": "libx264"
)
),
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"subtitles": 8
),
"retry": (
"run": 3,
"max": 9,
"delay": 30
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": true,
"scrub": false
)
聖なる夜
Holy night
4つの星が、ひとつになるとき
When four stars become one
奇跡が、はじまる。
The miracle begins.
さあ！
Come on!
Hyper Jumpin' 飛び越えよう
Hyper Jumpin', let's leap over
ハイになって ハイになるまで
Getting high until we're high
楽しんでいきたい
I want to have fun
Hyper Jumpin'!
Hyper Jumpin' 海の向こうまでも
Hyper Jumpin', even across the ocean
もっと もっと 近づきたいの
I want to get closer and closer
Hyper Jumpin'!
みるだけじゃない
It's not just about watching
いっしょになれるライブ
A live show where we can be together
360度 どこからも。
360 degrees, from everywhere.
もっと もっと 高く飛びたいの
I want to fly higher and higher
Hyper Jumpin' now!
ここにいる。手が触れそうなほど。
I'm here. Close enough to touch.
みるライブから、会えるライブへ。
From a live show you watch, to a live show where you meet.
ねぽらぼライブ参加方法
How to participate in NePoLaBo Live
ホロアースから参加する「ねぽらぼに会えるライブ」
Participate from Holoearth 'Live where you meet NePoLaBo'
動画配信サービスによる「視聴するライブ」
Video streaming service 'Live to watch'
ホロアースライブ 開催タイムスケジュール
Holoearth Live Event Schedule
初回ライブ：2025年12月21日(日) 19:00
First Live: Sunday, December 21, 2025, 19:00
ねぽらぼライブ記念Tシャツ Amazonにて販売中！
NePoLaBo Live Commemorative T-shirts now on sale on Amazon!
ねぽらぼライブ フォトコンテスト
NePoLaBo Live Photo Contest
ねぽらぼライブ参加方法
How to Participate in NePolabo Live
ホロアースからの参加
IDカードホルダーを購入してライブ会場に入場
Participating from Holoearth
Purchase an ID card holder to enter the live venue
ホロアースライブ開催タイムスケジュール
Holoearth Live Schedule
ねぽらぼ応援セット
ねぽらぼライブ応援グッズ＋IDカードホルダー付き
NePolabo Support Set
Support Goods + ID Card Holder included
デジタルグッズ（ホロアースのアイテム）
Digital Goods (Holoearth Items)
ねぽらぼライブ記念Tシャツ
Amazonにて販売中！
NePolabo Live Memorial T-shirt
Now on sale on Amazon!
ねぽらぼライブ フォトコンテスト
あなたが公式カメラマンに！
NePolabo Live Photo Contest
You become the official photographer!
聖なる夜
A holy night.
4つの星が、ひとつになるとき
When four stars become one...
奇跡が、はじまる。
A miracle begins.
さあ！
Now!
Hyper Jumpin' 飛び越えよう！
Hyper Jumpin'! Let's leap over!
ハイになって　ハイになるまで
Keep going 'til we're high, 'til we're on a high...
飛ばしていかな
We've gotta blast off!
Hyper Jumpin' 海の向こうまでも
Hyper Jumpin', even across the ocean!
もっと 近づきたいの
I want to get even closer!
みるだけじゃない
It's not just about watching.
いっしょになれるライブ
A live performance where we can be together.
360度、どこからも。
360 degrees, from anywhere.
みんな、ありがとう！
Thank you, everyone!
もっと高く飛びたいの
I want to jump even higher!
Hyper Jumpin' Now!
ここにいる。
I'm here.
手が触れそうなほど。
So close I could almost touch you.
Hyper Jumpin' Now!
みるライブから、会えるライブへ。
From a live to watch, to a live to meet.
聖なる夜
Holy Night
4つの星が、ひとつになるとき
When four stars become one
奇跡が、はじまる。
The miracle begins.
さあ
Now!
Hyper Jumpin' 飛び越えよう
Hyper Jumpin', let's jump over
派手になってハイになるまで足して行け
Add it up until it gets flashy and high
Hyper Jumpin' 雲の向こうまで
Hyper Jumpin', to the other side of the clouds
もっと もっと 近づきたいの
I want to get closer, more and more
みるだけじゃない
Not just watching
いっしょになれるライブ
A live where we can be together
360度、どこからも。
From anywhere, 360 degrees.
もっと もっと 高く飛びたいの
I want to fly higher, more and more
Hyper Jumpin' now!
ここにいる。
I am here.
手が触れそうなほど。
Close enough to touch.
2025.12.21 Sun / 出演 桃鈴ねね 尾丸ポルカ 雪花ラミィ 獅白ぼたん
2025.12.21 Sun / Cast: Momosuzu Nene, Omaru Polka, Yukihana Lamy, Shishiro Botan
会場 HOLOEARTH
Venue: HOLOEARTH
みるライブから、会えるライブへ。
From a live you watch, to a live you can meet at.
ねぽらぼライブ 参加方法
How to Participate in Nepolabo Live
ホロアースからの参加 / IDカードホルダーを購入してライブ会場に入場
Participation from Holoearth / Buy an ID card holder to enter the venue
ホロアースライブ 開催タイムスケジュール
Holoearth Live Schedule
ねぽらぼ応援セット
Nepolabo Support Set
デジタルグッズ（ホロアースのアイテム）
Digital Goods (Holoearth Items)
ねぽらぼライブ記念Tシャツ
Nepolabo Live Commemorative T-shirt
ねぽらぼライブ フォトコンテスト
Nepolabo Live Photo Contest
ねぽらぼライブ参加方法
How to participate in Nepolabo Live
ホロアースからの参加
IDカードホルダーを購入してライブ会場に入場
Participating from Holoearth:
Purchase an ID card holder to enter the live venue
ホロアースライブ開催タイムスケジュール
Holoearth Live schedule
ねぽらぼ応援セット
Nepolabo support set
デジタルグッズ（ホロアースのアイテム）
Digital goods (Holoearth items)
ねぽらぼライブ記念Tシャツ
Nepolabo Live memorial T-shirt
ねぽらぼライブフォトコンテスト
Nepolabo Live photo contest
聖なる夜
Holy night
4つの星が、ひとつになるとき
When four stars become one
奇跡が、はじまる。
A miracle begins.
さぁ
Come on
Hyper Jumpin'
飛び越えよう
Let's jump over
ハイになって
Get high
ハイになるまで
Until we get high
ダンスしてきな
Keep on dancing
Hyper Jumpin'
海の向こう
Beyond the ocean
までもっと
Even further
近づきたいの
I want to get closer
Oh oh oh...
みるだけじゃない
Not just watching
いっしょになれるライブ
A live show where we can be together
Ready to star...
Oh oh oh...
360度 どこからも。
360 degrees, from anywhere.
Oh oh oh...
もっと
More
高く飛びたいの
I want to jump higher
Hyper Jumpin' Now
ここにいる。手が触れそうなほど。
Right here. So close I could almost touch it.
みるライブから、会えるライブへ。
From a concert you watch, to a concert you encounter.
聖なる夜
Holy night
4つの星が、ひとつになるとき
When four stars become one
奇跡が、はじまる。
A miracle begins.
さあ
Come on!
Hyper Jumpin' 飛び越えよう
Hyper Jumpin', let's jump over it
ハイになって ハイになるまで
Get high, until you're high
楽しんできな
Go have fun
Hyper Jumpin' 海の向こうまでも
Hyper Jumpin', even beyond the sea
もっと近づきたいの
I want to get even closer
みるだけじゃない
It's not just for watching
いっしょになれるライブ
A live where we can be together
360度 どこからも
From any angle, 360 degrees
もっと高く飛びたいの
I want to jump even higher
Hyper Jumpin' now
ここにいる。手が触れそうなほど。
I'm here. Close enough to touch.
Hyper Jumpin' now
2025.12.21 Sun
出演：桃鈴ねね 尾丸ポルカ 雪花ラミィ 獅白ぼたん
Sunday, December 21, 2025
Cast: Momosuzu Nene, Omaru Polka, Yukihana Lamy, Shishiro Botan
会場：HOLOEARTH
Venue: HOLOEARTH
みるライブから、会えるライブへ。
From a live you watch, to a live where you can meet.
ねぽらぼライブ参加方法
How to Join NePoLaBo Live
ホロアースからの参加
IDカードホルダーを購入してライブ会場に入場
Join via Holoearth
Purchase an ID card holder to enter the venue
ホロアースライブ 開催タイムスケジュール
Holoearth Live Schedule
ねぽらぼ応援セット
応援グッズ＋IDカードホルダー付き
NePoLaBo Support Set
Includes support goods and an ID card holder
デジタルグッズ (ホロアースのアイテム)
Digital Goods (Holoearth Items)
ねぽらぼライブ記念Tシャツ
NePoLaBo Live Memorial T-shirt
ねぽらぼライブ フォトコンテスト
NePoLaBo Live Photo Contest
聖なる夜
Holy night
4つの星が、ひとつになるとき
When four stars become one
奇跡が、はじまる。
A miracle begins.
さあ
Come on!
Hyper Jumpin' 飛び越えよう
Hyper Jumpin', let's jump over it
ハイになって ハイになるまで
Get high, until you're high
楽しんできな
Go have fun
Hyper Jumpin' 海の向こうまでも
Hyper Jumpin', even beyond the sea
もっと近づきたいの
I want to get even closer
みるだけじゃない
It's not just for watching
いっしょになれるライブ
A live where we can be together
360度 どこからも
From any angle, 360 degrees
もっと高く飛びたいの
I want to jump even higher
Hyper Jumpin' now
ここにいる。手が触れそうなほど。
I'm here. Close enough to touch.
Hyper Jumpin' now
2025.12.21 Sun
出演：桃鈴ねね 尾丸ポルカ 雪花ラミィ 獅白ぼたん
Sunday, December 21, 2025
Cast: Momosuzu Nene, Omaru Polka, Yukihana Lamy, Shishiro Botan
会場：HOLOEARTH
Venue: HOLOEARTH
みるライブから、会えるライブへ。
From a live you watch, to a live where you can meet.
ねぽらぼライブ参加方法
How to Join NePoLaBo Live
ホロアースからの参加
IDカードホルダーを購入してライブ会場に入場
Join via Holoearth
Purchase an ID card holder to enter the venue
ホロアースライブ 開催タイムスケジュール
Holoearth Live Schedule
ねぽらぼライブ参加方法
How to Participate in the NePoLaBo Live
ホロアースからの参加
IDカードホルダーを購入してライブ会場に入場
Participating from Holoearth
Enter the venue by purchasing an ID card holder
ホロアースライブ開催タイムスケジュール
Holoearth Live Event Schedule
ねぽらぼ応援セット
応援グッズ＋IDカードホルダー付き
NePoLaBo Support Set
Includes support goods + ID card holder
デジタルグッズ（ホロアースのアイテム）
ライブ記念Tシャツ / マスコット / 特製ペンライト
Digital Goods (Holoearth Items)
Live Memorial T-shirt / Mascot / Special Penlight
アクリルスタンド / アクリルパネル
Acrylic Stand / Acrylic Panel
ねぽらぼ文字プレート / クラッカー / 花火
NePoLaBo Text Plate / Party Popper / Fireworks
ねぽらぼ特製エモート
NePoLaBo Special Emotes
ねぽらぼライブ記念Tシャツ
Amazonにて販売中！
NePoLaBo Live Memorial T-shirt
Now on sale on Amazon!
ねぽらぼライブ フォトコンテスト
あなたが公式カメラマンに！
NePoLaBo Live Photo Contest
You can be the official photographer!
聖なる夜
Holy Night
4つの星が、ひとつになるとき
When four stars become one
奇跡が、はじまる。
The miracle begins.
さあ
Now!
Hyper Jumpin' 飛び越えよう
Hyper Jumpin', let's leap over!
ハイになって ハイになるまで 辿り着きな
Getting high, keep getting high until you reach it
Hyper Jumpin' 海の向こうまでも
Hyper Jumpin', even across the ocean
もっと もっと 近くに来たいの
I want to come closer and closer
Woah woah woah... いっしょになれるライブ
Woah woah woah... A live where we can be together
Woah woah woah... 360度 どこからも
Woah woah woah... From 360 degrees, everywhere
Woah woah woah... もっと もっと 高く飛びたいの
Woah woah woah... I want to jump higher and higher
Hyper Jumpin' now
2025.12.21 Sun / 出演
桃鈴ねね 尾丸ポルカ 雪花ラミィ 獅白ぼたん
2025.12.21 Sun / Performers
Momosuzu Nene, Omaru Polka, Yukihana Lamy, Shishiro Botan
会場 HOLOEARTH
Venue: HOLOEARTH
みるライブから、会えるライブへ。
From a live you watch, to a live you can meet at.
ねぽらぼライブ参加方法
How to Participate in the NePoLaBo Live
ホロアースライブ開催タイムスケジュール
Holoearth Live Event Schedule
デジタルグッズ（ホロアースのアイテム）
Digital Goods (Holoearth Items)
ピンポンパンポーン
Ding-dong-dang-dong
みなさん、メリークリスマス！
Everyone, Merry Christmas!
本日は、ねぽらぼライブ re:VISIONにご来場いただき、ありがとうございます。
Thank you all for coming to NePoLaBo Live re:VISION today.
ライブ開始はこの後、19時からの予定となっていますので、今しばらくお待ちください。
The live performance is scheduled to start at 7:00 PM, so please wait a little longer.
本公演のチラ見せ部分は、動画のYouTubeへの投稿が可能です。
You are allowed to post the sneak-peek portions of this performance to YouTube.
かー、しかーし！
Buuut... however!
他のSNSは、音声なしの30秒以内の動画の投稿をお願いします。
For other social media, please limit your posts to silent videos under 30 seconds.
静止画のスクリーンショットや、感想などは全編を通じて可能なので、いっぱい呟きお願いします！
Still screenshots and your comments can be posted anytime, so please tweet about it a lot!
はーい！
Yes!
禁止事項ですが、本公演のミラー配信、ならびに音声ありのライブ本編動画の一部SNSへの投稿となっています。
Forbidden acts include mirror streaming this event or posting the main live footage with audio to social media.
音声なしでも、30秒を超える動画のSNS投稿も禁止となっています。
Posting videos longer than 30 seconds to social media is prohibited, even without audio.
ルールを正しく守って、ライブを楽しんでください。
Please follow the rules correctly and enjoy the live show!
さて、みんな。
Well then, everyone.
遊びに来る準備はできてるかな？
Are you ready to come play?
ねねが描いたTシャツ着てる人いるかな？
Is anyone wearing the T-shirt Nene drew?
雪民さんたちがどんな姿で会いに来てくれるか楽しみ！
I'm looking forward to seeing how all you Yukimin come to meet us!
ホロアースのライブだから、好きな服装でライブ見れるのもいいよね。
Since it's a Holoearth live, it's great that you can watch in whatever outfit you like.
スクショも撮っていいみたいなので、色んな角度からたくさん撮ってほしいです！
It seems you can take screenshots too, so I want you to take plenty from various angles!
そう、普通のライブだと動いて見て回ったりはできないもんね。
Yeah, you can't usually move around and look from different spots at a normal live.
ねんたちの最高の写真、期待してるぞー！
I'm expecting some great photos of us!
というわけで、ライブ開始までもうしばらくお待ちください。
So, please wait a little longer until the live starts.
一緒にライブ盛り上がって行こー！
Let's get hyped for the live together!
おー！
Yeah!
Hyper Jumpin' Now
ねぽらぼライブ re:VISION 始まるぞー！
NePoLaBo Live re:VISION is starting!
Hyper Jumpin' Now
ちょっと早めのクリスマス、盛り上がっていくぞー！
A slightly early Christmas, let's get hyped!
Hyper Jumpin' 飛び出そうもっともっと
Hyper Jumpin' Let's jump out more and more
Baby 輝いて ハート急接近ピュア
Baby, shine, a pure heart's rapid approach
Hyper Jumpin' 夢の先まではもっともっと
Hyper Jumpin' To the other side of our dreams, more and more
刺激が欲しいの
I want some excitement
ハイ！みんなでジャンプして！
Hey! Everyone, jump!
ハイ！ハイ！ハイ！
Hey! Hey! Hey!
Hyper Jumpin' Now
ハイ！ハイ！ハイ！
Hey! Hey! Hey!
Hyper Jumpin'
子供じゃない はしゃぐ方がお得でしょ
I'm not a kid, it's better to have a blast, right?
ねねち！ねねち！ねねち！
Nenechi! Nenechi! Nenechi!
景気良く 空回りも一興でしょ
With high spirits, even spinning in circles is fun, right?
ポルカ！ポルカ！ポルカ！
Polka! Polka! Polka!
宵の中 飲み交わしまくるテンション
In the evening, drinking together in high spirits
ラミィ！ラミィ！ラミィ！
Lamy! Lamy! Lamy!
ハードを 乗りこなして進むミッション
A mission to ride out the hardship and move forward
ぼたん！ぼたん！ぼたん！
Botan! Botan! Botan!
このままスピード加速して
Accelerating the speed just like this
辿り着く先に 何があるんだろう
I wonder what lies at our destination
止まらない気持ちを叩きつけて
Throwing down our unstoppable feelings
次元を越えていこう (行くぞー！)
Let's cross dimensions! (Here we go!)
Hyper Jumpin' 飛び跳ねよう
Hyper Jumpin' Let's jump around
ハイになって ハイになるまで弾けてキラ
Get high, until you're high, burst and sparkle
Hyper Jumpin' 空の向こうまででも
Hyper Jumpin' Even to the other side of the sky
もっともっと 近づきたいの
I want to get closer, more and more
Wow oh oh Wow oh oh
ドキドキしたい君に Gimme Gimme High
I want to feel my heart throb, give me, give me high
Wow oh oh Wow oh oh
もっともっと 高く飛びたいの
I want to fly higher, more and more
ハイ！ハイ！360度楽しめてるかー！？
Hey! Hey! Are you enjoying the 360-degree view!?
ハイ！ハイ！
Hey! Hey!
Hyper Jumpin' Now
ハイ！みんなでジャンプ！ジャンプ！ハイ！ハイ！
Hey! Everyone jump! Jump! Hey! Hey!
Hyper Jumpin'
斜めから 攻めていけ ガチクエスチョン
Attacking from an angle, a serious question
ねねち！ねねち！ねねち！
Nenechi! Nenechi! Nenechi!
ネガティブを 切り裂いてくれるセンサー
A sensor that cuts through negativity
ポルカ！ポルカ！ポルカ！
Polka! Polka! Polka!
流れる コメントとかけ合いセッション
A session interacting with the flowing comments
ラミィ！ラミィ！ラミィ！
Lamy! Lamy! Lamy!
エイムを 鍛えて狙い打つフィクション
A fiction to train your aim and shoot your shot
ぼたん！ぼたん！ぼたん！ (3、2、1、打てー！)
Botan! Botan! Botan! (3, 2, 1, Fire!)
It's what I wanna 好きになるまま
It's what I wanna, just falling in love
邪魔するノイズ ぶち消せ Bang Bang Bang
Blast away the interfering noise, Bang Bang Bang
Jumping 飛び出すだけ 足は欲張って
Jumping, just jumping out, my feet are greedy
笑い飛ばして 蹴飛ばして イッキ Jump around now
Laugh it off, kick it away, all at once, Jump around now
このまま僕ら旅をして
Just like this, we'll go on a journey
辿り着く先に 何があるんだろう
I wonder what lies at our destination
信じた未来とリンクして
Linking with the future we believed in
次元を越えていこう
Let's cross dimensions
さぁ！
Come on!
Hyper Jumpin' 飛び越えよう
Hyper Jumpin' Let's jump over
Hyper Jumpin' ハイになって ハイになって まだのシンデレラ
Hyper Jumpin', getting high, getting high, still a Cinderella
Hyper Jumpin' 見る向こうまで
Hyper Jumpin', to see what's beyond
もっと もっと 近づきたいの
I want to get closer and closer
Woah...
ドキドキしたい キリキリ会いたい
I want my heart to throb, I want to see you so much
Woah...
もっと もっと 高く跳びたいの
I want to jump higher and higher
ハイ！ハイ！ハイ！ハイ！
Hi! Hi! Hi! Hi!
ハイ！ハイ！ハイ！ハイ！ハイ！ハイ！ Hyper Jumpin' Now!
Hi! Hi! Hi! Hi! Hi! Hi! Hyper Jumpin' Now!
バイバーイ！
Bye-bye!
hololive 5th Generation
ねぽらぼライブ re:VISION
Holoearth Live
hololive 5th Generation
NePolabo Live re:VISION
Holoearth Live
イエーイ！やったー！
Yeah! We did it!
みんな元気ー？元気いっぱいだよー！
Everyone, are you doing well? I'm full of energy!
というわけで自己紹介行きましょう！ねねちから！
Well then, let's move on to self-introductions! Starting with Nenechi!
じゃあ、みんな、アイテムとかの準備いいですか？
Now, everyone, are you ready with your items?
順番に行きますからね。みんなアイテムの準備してください。
We'll go in order. Everyone, please get your items ready.
ね・ぽ・ら・ぼで行くからね。どれくらい待つ？この準備。
We're going in the order of Ne-Po-La-Bo. How long should we wait?
ちょっと待ったほうがいいか。準備準備。みんなアイテム、ショートカットに入れておいてね。
Maybe we should wait a bit? Prepare, prepare. Put your items in the shortcuts.
1、2、3、4で行こう。ヨイショ！ヨイショ！3、2、1、はい、どうぞ、ねねさん。
Let's use 1, 2, 3, and 4. Heave-ho! Heave-ho! 3, 2, 1, okay, Nenechi-san, please!
はーい！じゃあみんな行くよ！飛んでね！
Okay! Here I go, everyone! Jump, okay!
ホロライブ5期生、ねぽらぼの「ね」。みんなの心の...
Hololive 5th Gen, NePolabo's 'Ne'. Everyone's heart's...
せーの、エナジードリンク！
Ready, ENERGY DRINK!
八重歯もまぶしい、ねねです！よろしくねー！
With a dazzling snaggletooth, I'm Nene! Nice to meet you!
じゃあ次、はい！切り替えて！切り替えて！
Okay next, yes! Switch! Switch!
尾丸ポルカだよー！いつものないか？
It's Omaru Polka! Is the usual one there?
ポルカおるか？おるやん！ねぽらぼの「ぽ」、尾丸ポルカです！よろしく！
Is Polka there? She is! NePolabo's 'Po', Omaru Polka! Nice to meet you!
こんらみー！ホロライブ5期生の雪花ラミィです。
Kon-Lamy! Hololive 5th Gen, Yukihana Lamy here.
ラミィちゃんしかー？勝たん！！雪花ラミィだぞー！はい、そして最後最後、
Only Lamy-chan is...? The best!! It's Yukihana Lamy! Okay, and finally, finally,
みんな準備して。OK、OK、準備してる？1UP、1UP持った？
everyone get ready. OK, OK, are you ready? Did you get the 1UP, 1UP?
準備してるよ。御布施、御布施。何か御布施あるじゃん。ラライア！
I'm ready. Offering, offering. There's some offering, right. La-Lion!
ホロライブ5期生、獅白ぼたんでーす。イエーイ！御代頂きます！頂きますよー！
Hololive 5th Gen, Shishiro Botan here. Yeah! I'll take the fee! I'm taking it!
はい、皆さんにバッチリ決まったところで、新しい試み、Re:VISIONライブということで、
Yes, now that we're all set, this is a new endeavor, the Re:VISION Live.
詳しいことは概要欄やホロアースの公式ホームページを確認してください。
For details, please check the description or the Holoearth official website.
ということで、今日はアバターで参加してるし、いろんな角度からのこの振り付け、確認してほしいなと思います。
So, since everyone is participating with avatars today, I hope you'll check out the choreography from various angles.
ねねの服着てる人はいると信じてるからね、みんな！いいよ、いいよ、いいよ、いいよ！
I believe there are people wearing Nene's clothes, okay everyone! Good, good, good, good!
みんなもっとよく見せて。あ、いいよ。いいよ。こっちが写真撮るんだね。
Everyone, show me more. Ah, good. Good. I'll be taking photos from here.
みんなとやれること何かない？ポルカ。よし、あれやろう、あれ。全力疾走しましょう、皆さん。
Isn't there something we can do with everyone, Polka? Okay, let's do that. Let's run at full speed, everyone.
走るよ、ここから。えーと、ポルカが先頭で、ぐるっと走ってみよう。
We're running, from here. Um, Polka will lead, let's try running around.
はい、OK。じゃあみんな集合集合！みんなついてきてね。
Yes, OK. Then everyone gather up! Everyone follow us, okay.
じゃあせーので行くか。ハイ！じゃあせーの！わー！先生、速いやつがいます！
Then, shall we go on 'se-no'? Yes! Then, se-no! Waaa! Teacher, there's a fast one!
待ってー！速いやつがいるー！ハイハイハイハイ！
Wait! There's a fast one! Hi, hi, hi, hi!
早くしてください。ぼたんさんがついてこれないよ。
Please slow down. Botan-san can't keep up.
大丈夫！あ、反対周り行きまーす！うわー！
It's okay! Ah, we're going the other way! Wooo!
先生、本気のやつがいます！大丈夫か？
Teacher, there's a serious one! Are you okay?
ハイ、本気のやつがいる。本気のやつがいる。あれれれれ、こっち。あれ、一周遅れ？
Yes, there's a serious one. Over here. Oh, is it a lap late?
ハイ、お疲れ様ー！みんなと走れて楽しいー！
Okay, good job everyone! It was fun running with everyone!
じゃあ、一緒に走れることなかなかないからね。あ、ちなみに、本番の曲の最中ですが、
Well, we don't get many chances to run together. Ah, by the way, during the actual songs,
周りの人がね、まあジャンプするとかが見えやすいように、
to make it easier to see when people around you jump,
配慮してください。ジャンプ！ピーピー！前周りの人に配慮して！
please be considerate. JUMP! PEE-PEE! Be considerate of the people in front!
配慮してピーピー！配慮して！
Be considerate, pee-pee! Be considerate!
ハイ！盛り上がってるところ申し訳ないんですが、
Yes! I'm sorry to interrupt while we're all fired up,
ここで悲しいお知らせがあります。何、何？
but I have a sad announcement here. What, what?
ということで皆さん、すみません。YouTubeと、ポータルスクエアでの無料配信はここまでとなっております。
So, everyone, I'm sorry. The free broadcast on YouTube and at the Portal Square ends here.
うわああああ！
Uwaaaaaa!
はい、すみません。
Okay, sorry.
引き続き、ねぽらぼライブ re:VISION、
Holoearth内では配信されますので、
Continuing on, Nepolabo Live re:VISION
will be streamed within Holoearth,
YouTubeで見ている方は、
動画の概要欄をチェックしてください。
so those watching on YouTube,
please check the description box.
はい！
Yes!
で、チケット持ってる方で、まだこっちに
来てないフォカルスクエアのみんなは、
And for those with tickets who haven't come
over from Focal Square yet,
よかったらこっちに来てください。
please come over if you'd like.
来てください！
Please come!
えー、じゃあ、というわけで...
Well then, in that case...
YouTubeのみんな、バイバーイ！
Everyone on YouTube, bye-bye!
バイバーイ！
Bye-bye!
さわやかだな。
How refreshing.
というわけで、次からはソロ曲ですが、
So, next up are solo songs,
まずは誰からかなー？
but who's going first?
誰ー？
Who?
誰かな？誰かな？
Who is it? Who is it?
ねねちゃーん！
Nene-chan!
それではよろしくお願いします！
Well then, please take it away!
みんな、どんどん盛り上がって、いくぞー！
Everyone, get more and more hyped! Let's go!
おー！
Oh!
無料パートは終了いたしました。
ご視聴ありがとうございました！
The sneak peek part of the show has ended.
Thank you for watching!